Good afternoon. Uh, thanks for joining
us. You're watching Drogram with me, Ted
R, and John Kuryaku. John, always good
to see you.
>> Good to see you, Ted.
>> Greetings from Salt Lake City, Utah.
>> Oh, good, good. I love Salt Lake City,
actually. U have I hope things are going
well out there. Uh, I have a feeling I
know what you're doing there, but you
know,
>> work, work, and more work.
>> Always, always,
>> always work.
>> Lots to talk about today. So, uh, we
should just I'm just going to give
everyone a preview of the show. Thanks
everyone for joining us. Um, we are now
fully monetized on Rumble thanks to you
guys. We'll be
>> amazing.
Amazing. Amazing in one day. So, thank
you everybody. Thank you very much.
Incredible
>> indeed. And, uh, please continue to
like, follow, and share the show. Uh,
we're here Monday, Wednesday, Friday at
5:00 PM Eastern time. Uh, in a couple of
weeks we'll be going to Monday through
Friday schedule, same time, 5:00 pm. So,
uh, you know, you got this show is
growing by leaps and bounds. Thanks to
you guys. You guys are awesome. Thank
you. All right. Lots to talk about. I
don't know what order we're going to do
it in because I always have an order in
mind, but we end up just talking. May I
suggest something? Actually,
>> I hope you don't mind if I interrupt
you. Not at all.
>> One one hour ago,
>> Gileain Maxwell was transferred to a
minimum security
>> uh prison in Texas. And the transfer was
confirmed by the
>> the Bureau of Prisons.
I how why
would this possibly happen?
I mean, I I'm I'm speechless. I don't
even know what to say. It It seems like
some sort of a a quid proquo,
right?
>> Well, what I've the best I've been able
to I did a lot of reading on this and
the best explanation I was able to
garner was pos cooperating witnesses
sometimes can negotiate this sort of
thing. This is they call this a clubfed
type situation. That's right. And as
you've pointed but you pointed out, I
mean, so she's a cho, right? She's a
child molester by definition, convicted.
She can't sue us for it because it's
true. Uh at least a jury of her peers
determined it to be true.
>> That's right.
>> So, um she but normally they're in
minimum, right? You've explained that
before.
>> Normally they're in low
>> low.
>> They're not eligible for minimum
>> between low and minimum.
minimum has no uh bars on the windows,
no locks on the doors. You're free to
come and go as you please. You're just
on your honor, not to abscond.
Um
>> it's like a dorm. It's like a campus
situation.
>> Yeah, exactly. They're the ones that
will will drive
um higher security prisoners to the
doctor's office or, you know, along with
with guards. They'll tend the the garden
in the wardens on the warden's property.
They're the trustees is what it comes
down to. And and a lot of them in the
prison where I was in um a lot of them
uh worked janitorial jobs in the at the
university in the in the town,
but you can't trust if somebody's been
accused or been convicted of a child sex
crime, by definition, they're not
allowed in a minimum security camp.
Would minimum security camp be a prequel
to uh an earlier release than
>> it? Almost always is. Yes. So, here's
the rule with that. Most people short of
murder or something incredibly violent
or what's called what's called level 40
on the sentencing scale. That's like El
Chapo, for example.
>> Okay. If you're below that,
um, with good behavior and the passage
of time, you work your way down from a
maximum to a medium to a low to a
minimum and then they let you go.
>> So, you're not allowed to be in
a low if you have more than 20 years on
your sentence, unless you're a cho
and then for your own safety, you're in
the low.
>> Okay? Once you get under 10 years, you
can transfer into the minimum
unless you're a chomo, in which case
you're not allowed in the minimum. So,
so she defies this rule in two different
ways. She has 20 years
and she's a chomo.
So, how in the world did she wake up
today and get transferred to a minimum
security camp?
>> Well, so let's speculate. Um, you know,
if you listened to everything we've said
on this show so far and you bet on it in
Vegas, you're rich. We've been on a roll
lately. Yeah.
>> So, uh, let's let's see if we can keep
that going here. Is she going to get out
and if so, what kind of deal did she cut
and why? I mean, it's so hard to figure
out, you know, what the Trump
administration DOJ is on about here,
right? I mean, it seems like first they
were going to be transparent. Then they
looked like they're indel in wallowing
in a full-fledged cover up. They kicked
the House of Representatives home early.
>> Yeah.
>> To to cover it up. But now, if she's
making a deal, the deal is is not for
her to stay.
>> Yes.
>> It's not for her to be quiet. It's her
to talk. Or is it?
[Music]
>> That's what it sounds like. That's what
it seems like. She's cut some sort of a
deal. Now, nobody's going to say what
the deal is. Now, the deal could be, "I
will talk to you and testify if you
don't charge me with any new crimes, and
by the way, I want to go to a camp." And
then she's going to be in the camp for
the next 17 years.
Or
I'll tell you whatever you want to know
if you give me a pardon or a
commutation. Oh, and by the way, I don't
want to go back to that low security
because uh I don't I don't like the the
times moves. I want to go to a camp. We
we don't
>> Or or is it we want you to go out and
confirm the story we've told the world,
which was that it was only Jeffrey?
>> That's right. That's right.
>> I mean, it was only Jeffrey.
>> And I think I think Bam.
That's it,
>> man. I don'tide myself.
>> What else could it be, though, right? I
mean, it's not like she's going to come
out. She's she's they're they're letting
her out to cut a deal to say, "Oh, and
by the way, Trump was there, right?" Or,
"Oh, by the way, Bill Clinton was
there." I mean, maybe Bill Clinton, but
not you know what I mean?
>> Just stunning. I just can't believe it.
Virginia Duffy's family was on uh
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I was watching CNN on the plane
>> and and they were I mean, they were like
on the brink of tears. Every one of
them.
>> They couldn't believe it.
>> No, they couldn't believe it. So, yeah.
So, so she's probably going to get out,
right? Better than 50/50.
>> I would I would put it at better than
50/50. Yes. If only because this
president is so unpredictable when it
comes to commutations and pardons. And,
you know, for 95%
I I I'm I'm all for it. I'm I'm hoping
he does more, including me. But, uh but
this one this one's a a kick in the gut.
Well, I mean it would this would pretty
much Well, here's a question, right?
Let's let's say she we're right. She
gets out. She confirms the official
narrative that we heard from AG uh
Bondi.
Does that get Magaw World off Trump's
back or does it get enough of Magaw
World off his back that he can start to
chill and think about other things?
>> That's a good question. But did you
happen to see on Fox yesterday their um
their new polls? So the polls have
Democrats like 93-7
they want her to rot in prison
>> and independents were like 7327
and then Republicans were 50/50.
So I think we're quickly getting to the
point where Donald Trump doesn't care.
He doesn't care what Democrats and
independents are saying about this
>> mag he never cares what they think at
all.
>> Yeah. I mean,
>> the world's coming around to it.
>> He's proven something that I've been
saying for years is that there are no
moderates. There are no fence sitters.
There are no swing voters. There's only
base voting. Democrats haven't figured
it out yet.
>> Yeah.
>> They they think there's still a
mysterious swing voter out there.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> Out like this.
>> Let's just sit sit with this for like 10
seconds. then literally no one will have
been punished or held to account for
Jeffrey Epstein except Jeffrey Epstein
who theoretically held himself to
account theoretically.
>> Yeah. I think that's the painful truth
right there. That's what it is.
>> Wow. Okay. Well, that's and
>> it kind of reminds me of the torture
program. Like the only guy who went to
prison was the guy who who blew the
whistle on the torture program. But
that's just me. I'm biased.
>> Yeah, you're so bitter, John. Why don't
you just move on? Why don't you just put
it past you,
Zen? Oh,
>> that's what I need. And I need my gun
back. Gun back.
>> I'm not sure you should have your gun
back right now. Not Not in the next
hour, anyway. All right. So, we'll we'll
keep we'll keep up uh we'll keep people
up to up to date on that. By the way,
other break late breaking news. Um so uh
you know usually when presidents get bad
get bad jobs numbers they cry into and
uh maybe they call the Fed. Uh this time
uh you know kill the messenger. He
decided to throw the head of the Bureau
of Labor Statistics down a well. Trump
has fired the chief of the Bureau of
Labor Statistics. Um which is
>> I laughed out loud when I read it.
>> It's hilarious. I mean, first of all,
it, you know, you have to think when you
get that job as like a statistician,
like you went to like MIT and you're a
stat, you're a statistics expert. You're
like, I'm working for the government.
Yeah, but it's the safest job in
Washington. Who's going to fire me? All
I do is crunch numbers. I mean,
>> well, things change.
>> Um, do we want to talk? Do we want to
talk about that? Do we care? Sure.
There's plenty more to talk about.
>> Yeah. Um,
I don't mean to laugh, but it's just so
absurd that I can't help it to laugh.
>> No, I mean it it's look, it's obviously
wrong. I mean, the funny part is, of
course, that this just the jobs numbers
have been manipulated for years, right?
There's the question like if you gave up
looking for work, you're not counted as
unemployed anymore. If it's a certain
amount of time that you've been
unemployed, you're not counted un as
unemployed. They calculate the um you
know a lot of other statistics as well,
the size of the labor participation
uh rate, but all of that for all of
their shenanigans, these are usually
political decisions that come from
people like President Trump. Um it's not
they're not, you know, they're just
crunching the numbers over there. I
mean, as far as I know, there's never
ever been the slightest accusation, much
less evidence, that anyone in her
position or her, has ever done what
Trump is accusing her of.
She should sue. She should sue.
>> She should sue. The numbers are the
numbers. That's it.
>> That's it. It's It's really as simple as
that. It's They just put it into the
>> You think this is going to get the the
the stock traders off his ass? The bond
traders,
>> right? I mean, the market I've been so
busy I haven't I haven't seen it since
it closed, but it was down Well, it's
down seven.
>> What did it fall to?
>> It was down a full percent. Um
>> Yeah, that that that was the last I I
had seen. it was down a full percent
after having been down almost 2%.
>> But that was also because of the uh the
tar the tariffs and uh yeah the new
tariffs on Canada.
>> By the way uh you know I didn't put this
in to talk about but I thought it was
worth noting the econ even the threat of
the tariffs against Lotho
>> literally destroyed the Lothan economy.
Trump uh threatened 50% tariffs only
imposed the 15 that he imposed on
everyone else. Nevertheless, uh just the
mere threat of that tanked the the all
these factories that were forced to
close um just because Trump didn't
understand the nature of the economy.
Well, South is a welfare state and
basically Congress a while ago basically
had put zero tariffs on them just to
encourage them to sell like, you know,
textiles and other trinkets to the
American market. You know, stuff that
would show up at tier one imports, that
kind of stuff. And and of course, and
then Trump just looks at the numbers.
It's like, we have a trade deficit. They
don't buy anything from us. Oh, they'd
love to. They're just broke. They don't
have any money at all.
>> They're among the poorest people in the
world,
>> right? And so people, they're just
heartbroken and desperate now. They
don't even know how they're going to
eat. It's just a reflection of how, you
know, the unintended consequences of
someone who's just sort of like making
decisions quickly without really
non-reflexively
uh you know, can can these things can
play out. Um, so yeah, the market, you
know, Bill Clinton in his uh biography,
autobiography, he said it's not a very
good book. I don't recommend it. But
>> you know why? Because he wrote it
himself.
>> Oh, did he?
>> Yeah.
>> It's not a good book. I read it, too,
and it was like,
>> and I love presidential autobiography.
>> Me, too. He should have he should have
hired a ghostriter.
>> The best ones are Grant and Truman, in
my opinion. Um,
>> agreed. Grant is epic.
>> Not a president. Cordell Hull, former
Secretary of State. His is excellent
too. Fantastic. Anyway, point is that uh
in in Clinton's book though, one of the
things that I thought was really
interesting is he said, you know, I
really thought I was elected president
of the United States, but I was really
elected president of the bond market. I
spent all of my time thinking about the
bond market. I'm sure that hasn't
changed.
>> No, 100%. I think that's exactly right.
That's exactly right. you know, um he's
the last couple of days he's made
additional threats besides against the
Canadians, which we saw in the Canadians
responded to, but against Brazil. You
know, he's been trying to get these
impeachment proceedings and criminal
charges dropped against U. President uh
what was his name? The former president
of Brazil before Lula um whatever his
name was, the Trump guy. And um
am I still shadowbanned? I don't think
that's true.
>> I was, but I don't think I am anymore.
>> No, because I found you a couple days
ago and everything came up no problem.
>> Oh, good. Yeah, Bossaro. Um, they're
just letting, you know, the the criminal
justice system do its thing. And now, in
addition to having put
sanctions on the on the judge in the
case, now they're talking about adding
tariffs on Brazil unless the Brazilians
drop the drop the charges. It's nuts.
>> Well, and let's not forget, we're going
to be talking about Gaza. We can talk
about Gaza now, but um Trump also hiked
up the san um the tariffs on Canada
because for as retaliation for
recognizing Palestine.
>> Yeah, it's crazy.
>> I mean,
>> after after having said what, a week ago
when they said that they were thinking
of doing it or maybe it was at the G7,
um he said, um I respect that. I won't
do it, but I respect that. Well,
actually, he doesn't respect that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's It's crazy. Um,
well, shall we get into uh Oh, we should
get in. There's so much to talk about
Gaza, right? So,
>> Oh my god. Yeah.
>> In uh No. Well, before we do that, let's
talk. Let's uh bring in producer Robbie
on to Yes. One more pitch here to Right.
We promise we're not going to do this
every single show, but until we have the
numbers cooking, we have to do this. So,
very quickly, producer Robbie West,
thank you so much for coming on. Uh,
please explain to the good folks
watching on YouTube why it would be
awesome for John and I if uh with some
of if they were to migrate over to
Rumble to watch.
>> Well, well, to migrate or at least just
go over there and hang out and chat and
such. So, to make this short and sweet,
basically, for every quarter that
YouTube will pay uh Ted and John, now
they're in their now that they are in
the creator program,
Rumble will pay them over a dollar.
>> It's crazy.
>> So, it's kind of a dumb way to kind of
to kind of break it down, but the gist
of it is it's all about paying the
bills, folks. Uh the Biden regime, they
killed their jobs. I mean, y'all know
what's I mean, everyone needs to have
money, right? You gota have money to pay
your bills. You got to have money to
live. Uh, YouTube YouTube will pay a
little bit. Rumble pays a whole hell of
a lot more. And the best part about it
is that Rumble pays you based off of
>> John's got legal bills up the ass.
>> Oh my god.
>> And and Yeah. And I' I've been living
off my savings since last September when
Biden fired us.
>> Yeah. And I mean, that's what it's all
about, right? So, Rumble is a free
speech platform. It is alternative to
YouTube.
Rumble also pays significantly better.
And y'all going to see that in action
here in just a little bit because
Rumble's actually giving us ads that
we're able to to put out on ourselves
that then go directly in to John's and
Ted's coffers. So, one of the things I'm
going to be doing is going through just
putting in just videos addition to live
streams. And really all we ask is that
if you go over there, if you follow them
on Rumble, just know if you watch them
there. Watch hours on YouTube mean
nothing. Watch hours mean the world over
on Rumble. It's like TV. If a if a TV
show is high ratings, you get paid more.
Rumble's the exact same way. And lastly,
Rumble will let them say things that
YouTube will not allow them to say
because there's going to be at least
five hours a month of what they call
Rumble Premium of Content
where it's only going to be available on
Rumble.
And these these two fellas already don't
have much of a filter. They'll have no
filter whenever they're live on Rumble.
So, if you want to hear just live
unbarnished truth, make the jump over to
Rumble.
>> All right, Robbie, thank you so much.
And thank you guys for listening to all
that. Um,
>> thank you.
>> And and Robbie, when you're ready, we'll
read that first ad. Go ahead and put it
up when you're ready. Um, all right. So,
let me take Robbie out of here. Okay.
So, Pal, uh, Gaza Palestine. So, it's
hard to know where to start. 147 people
have died of famine according to the
Gaza Health Ministry. As always, we must
point out that contrary to what the
Zionists say. That's not an overcount.
It is a radical underount because in
order to be counted, they have to have
your um they have to have your full
name, your body, your age, your ID
number, and your occupation. And you
know, if you died somewhere else,
they're not bringing and you don't go to
the hospital, they don't count you. If
you if you die in a basement somewhere,
they don't count you. So, uh and also
you don't really count if you died of
something else that's maybe hunger
related, like you succumb to an illness
that you might have survived if you were
stronger. So, 147 dead of famine. Uh
let's go ahead and read this ad very
quickly. Uh all right. All right,
anglers. If you're ready to fish remote
lakes or quiet rivers in total stealth
mode, check out the Nevada Fishing Float
Tube from Catis Sports. This U-shaped
beast is built for serious fishing
missions. Ultra stable, ultra
maneuverable, and tough as nails thanks
to heavyduty riptop material and double
stitched seams. You get a padded back
rest, oversized seat, two large gear
pockets, rod holder, sh uh stripping
apron, and even a dryfly patch.
Everything you need to stay locked in
and ready when the bite is on.
Fluorescent accents keep you visible out
on the water and carry handles make it
easy to haul in and out. Whether you're
chasing bass in the shallows or hiking
into alpine trout lakes, the Nevada
float tube is built for the job. Use
code rumble at checkout for 10% off your
order today. That's katapasports.com.
Get out there, stay light, and catch the
big one. All right, that was fun.
>> Sounds great.
>> I I kind of want I kind of want one of
those things.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it sounds great. So, all
right. So, famine in Gaza, these people
who probably don't they're thinking
about other things than trout fishing.
Um, so the the world is furious. Uh,
countries are recognizing uh Palestine
right and left. And just after we went
off the air on Wednesday, John, uh, news
broke that Germany, the country that we
thought would be second to last,
penultimate after, uh, that basically
second to last to go after before the
US, is now considering formal uh,
diplomatic recognition of of uh,
Palestine. They haven't decided to do
it. They're on the fence.
>> Incredible.
>> You know, the world is changing.
It's changing a little too slowly for my
liking, but it's it's changing
>> and for the people of Palestine.
>> That's right.
>> But it's great. It's great that they're
doing it. Um, by the way, I want to
thank uh over on Rumble, we've gotten
some donations from uh USCXS21.
Thank you very much. And thank you very
much for at Gracemeister. Much
appreciated for those financial
contributions. Okay, so um
>> what do you think is going to happen
there in Germany? It seems like um the
you know France basically broke broke
broke the dam for most of Europe and for
the civilized world. Australia is coming
soon. Um I don't know what's happening
with New Zealand but if Ger it seems
like the UK may have been the lynch pin
for Germany,
>> right? I don't know. Um certainly the UK
is was the lynch pin to Canada and now
for Australia.
>> Yes, I was just going to say that. And
you know, I'm I'm wondering too, the
German leadership is weak, as weak as
it's been in a in decades, and I'm
wondering if they don't want to be sort
of left behind at the dance,
and so they're considering jumping in.
Now, the Washington Post this morning
had a graphic. It was a map of the
world, and it showed all the um all the
countries that have diplomatic relations
with Palestine and the countries that
don't. Well, the countries that don't
were the US, Canada, and the European
Union. Everybody else in the world has
diplomatic relations with Palestine.
So, this is very big news for us. It's
not so big for the rest of the world
because they're wondering, you know,
what's taken you guys so long, but maybe
finally, you know, there's going to be
some way to help Palestinians.
So, John, I you know, I've been thinking
a little bit about like, you know, my
friends who are pro-Zionist um are
saying, "Well, this isn't a big deal."
You know, there's there's no state
really to recognize because there's no n
there's no real there's not even one
government to recognize. Uh there may be
that the one that they do recognize is
corrupt and broken. Yeah. What's the
point here? And I think the point here
is that the symbolism is going to have
profound economic consequences. I was
thinking, you know, just yesterday, what
if I got a job offer to go draw cartoons
for the Times of Israel, and let's say
they even said you can do anything you
want. You can criticize Netanyahu.
>> I don't think I could take that job.
>> Um I I think Jerusalem Post used to be
very legit. I could think about Ha Arts.
>> That's it. It's the only one I could
think about. Um, you know, if I'm a tech
bro, uh, you know, if I if I'm off, you
know, do I do a deal with an Israeli
tech company, um, I don't think I can.
Um, you know, I think I'll I'll catch
too much [__] from my employees and from
my customers. Um, you know, basically,
it used to be, think about six months
ago, John, it was exactly the opposite.
If you refuse to do business with, you
know, with Israel, you'd be accused of
anti-semitism.
Now the howling Holocaust and
anti-semitism,
>> it doesn't work anymore. It's the boy
who cried wolf. It's done. It's over.
And I mean, the spell is broken, right?
And um and people, so it's going to hurt
them. This is a country that doesn't
really have natural resources and you
know, at all. It has a tech sector
that's completely dependent on
international, western, specifically US
support. That sector is going to go
away. They're going to be like South
Africa during apartheid but worse
because South Africa is a mineralrich
country. They have their own economy.
They didn't really need anyone else.
They were very self- sustaining.
>> Yes.
>> Israel's not it's a welfare state.
They're going to feel the hurt within
months.
>> Oh man, I I agree. And not that this
necessarily will lead to anything, but
we we spoke on the last episode about
this um or two episodes ago about this
vote in the House of Representatives uh
over whether to cut off um offensive
military aid. It it had six votes. It
was all members of the uh of the squad
plus uh Marjorie Taylor Green. Well,
there was an identical vote in the
Senate last night and 27 senators, all
Democrats,
>> yes,
>> voted in favor. So, we're talking about
we're talking about what 1 and a half%
of the House a week ago, but now 27% of
the Senate voting to cut off offensive
military aid. I think that's dramatic.
>> It is dramatic. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. and and and and senators are, you
know, they're that the Senate is the
slow deliberative body, right?
>> That's right. The one that we're
supposed to take so seriously because
they're supposed to be the adults in the
room.
>> Well, they are they are being the adults
in the room,
>> right?
>> I mean, obviously, they need to get to
50 and and 60 and beyond,
>> right?
>> Will they
>> uh not in the near term? No.
>> No.
>> A still too powerful.
>> Yeah. But you know, we used to say we
used to say no relative to South Africa,
too. You remember Ronald Reagan
just told everybody just get it out of
your heads. We're not sanctioning South
Africa. We're going to we're going to
have relations with South Africa. We're
going to we're going to trade with South
Africa and nothing's going to change.
And then two years after a year a year
after Reagan left the presidency, uh the
apartheid government fell.
Uh, Houdini always has good questions.
Uh, not no shade on anyone else here.
What happens if the EU doesn't recognize
Palestine, but a member nation does?
>> Well, that's already happened.
>> Yes.
>> With Ireland.
>> And Spain.
>> And Spain. Yeah.
>> And it's going to happen with Croatia.
>> Yes, it will.
>> So, um,
>> yes, it will.
>> So, um, I don't think it ma I don't
think it matters, right? I mean, is EU
recognition important really? I mean,
I'm not sure
>> as an organization.
>> I mean, you know, like if you're
Palestine, how much do you care about
the EU? It seems like you probably get
you care about everything.
>> Yeah. Unless you just want you want a
presence in Brussels.
>> Yeah.
>> You want everything.
>> Yeah. If I were Palestinian, I'd say I'd
say sure. I I would want EU recognition.
Sure.
But I just don't I you know I mean I I
will say I think the France thing ended
up being the big game changer and uh you
know again good job President Mcron I
mean yeah he really helps uh vindicate
his own legacy after because he's a very
unpopular guy
>> very unpopular
>> but this is popular.
>> Uhhuh. It is.
>> I heard somebody dismiss it the other
day saying well half of France is Muslim
anyway. No. 10% of France is Muslim.
>> Yeah. More than you'd think, actually.
>> Yeah. But a majority of
>> It's a Catholic country. They don't go
to mass ever.
>> No.
>> At all. No.
>> No. Um,
>> let's talk a little bit about uh this.
This really uh I didn't know whether to
laugh or to cry, but I thought it was a
huge story symbolically. So, a a pel of
IDF soldiers went to visit the death
camp at Burkanau. And like as has
happened in the past when uh pro-Israeli
or Israeli people have gone to Ashvitz
or any of the death camps, they came
draped with Israel, Israeli flags,
>> they were turned away for the first time
this week. Wow.
>> Uh and they were told by the uh people
who control, you know, it's a museum now
who control it saying um this is a site
of genocide. Um you can't bring that in.
It's a si the that is a symbol of
genocide.
>> Wow.
>> And that's never happened before. I I
just it was it blew me away.
>> Oh, I'm I'm impressed.
You know, there was a uh there was
another kurfuffle on on my ancestral
island of roads last week. um an Israeli
um cruise ship docked and um and a mob
of of Greeks formed and would let them
the tourists off the ship. Now roads
>> survives on tourism,
>> right?
>> And Greece and Israel are very close.
They would not let them off the ship. So
there were some IDF guys that were
escorting the ship. They came off, a
fight broke out, they got back on the
ship and the ship went away presumably
to, you know, Turkey or Cypress or
whatever. But um again this morning
there was a group of Israeli tourists
that flew in. There are direct flights
to roads from everywhere. You don't have
to go through Athens. You can come
directly from Tel Aviv. You can come
from London, any of the Scandinavian
countries. And so this group of Israeli
tourists um went in and they're just
walking around the medieval city and
this mob formed
and they were so the Israelis were so
afraid that they would be beaten. They
probably would have been
>> Whoa.
>> Um that they uh they left the medieval
town called the old city and um and went
back to the airport.
>> Wow. I mean
>> at times they are a changing. The only
thing that troubles me about that, of
course, is, you know, that, you know,
just because someone's Israeli does not
mean that they approve of what's going
on. Although, according to the polls,
the odds are that they do.
>> Right.
>> Um, okay. So, let's talk a little bit
about So, I did want to say, yes, RD s
we should talk about the French Algerian
war.
>> Everybody should learn about the French
Algerian war. It's that important.
>> One big recommendation. Yeah. Well,
after 911, right, my understanding is
that the Pentagon um showed the 1966
French film, the pseudo documentary, The
Battle of Alers, um in order to try to
show like what the conflict between the
col colonialist West and uh and the
Muslim uh occupied uh world was like. Um
it's a it's a it's black and white. It
moves incredibly fast. It's a brilliant
film and it's meant to it's it's all
historically accurate and it's meant to
look like news reels. It's meant to look
like it's real footage, but it's not.
It's our it's it's all filmed that way.
Uh but it depicts this amazing event.
And you know I always like to say that
the difference between France and the
United States is that Charles de Gaul
who was the biggest advocate of of you
know La France Ala French Algeria
forever.
>> He goes to you know factf finding trip
on the ground to Alers. He finds out
they [__] hate us. They don't want us
here.
>> And he came back home went on national
television and told the French people I
was [__] wrong. Like they they hate
us. we can't be there. We have to
withdraw and we have to help them become
independent and finance them and like
help them land on their feet and the
French and a lot of pe the right-wingers
absolutely hated him for it. But that
was an act of integrity
>> and you know we just don't we don't
admit that kind of thing.
>> No, it was like Walter Kankite going to
Vietnam and then coming back and saying
oh my god was I wrong.
And that's when Lyndon Johnson said he
knew we had lost the war. when he lost
Kronhite,
>> although Konite wasn't really
very in favor of the war, right? I mean,
I think he was kind of like, "Whatever."
>> He kind of went along with the
government line,
>> you know, we're the good guys. They're
the they're communists. We have to stop
them.
>> Yeah. And then he showed
>> then over there, then over here,
>> all those old excuses.
>> And then let's uh you know, so also uh
let's talk about Steve Whit. He had his
little He had his little uh vacations
all I ever wanted.
>> He would not allow any anybody from the
media to go.
>> Yes. So he allowed himself to be used as
a prop. The Israelis trundled him over
to one of these food distribution sites
run by the disastrous Gaza and
hilariously named humanitarian
foundation which have all been basically
pigshoots. Um, you know, ba basically
they they put these the Palestinians are
all like basically forced into tight
little fenced in cages in the heat
without water. Uh, and uh, if they get
too spicy, the Israelis shoot them.
>> Um, and it's been literally happening
every single day. Yes. Sometimes a
hundred people a day. Um, but at least,
you know, 20 is a slow day when it comes
to the Israelis killing people to get
food. Um, at these sites there's only
four. Gaza is not so big, but um,
there's there are people who would be
required to hike maybe five miles at
least round through a war zone, an
active combat zone, round trip from
where they're camped to these food
distribution sites where they might be
killed. I mean, no wonder, you know, the
the the food aid isn't getting where it
needs to be. And it's it's a, you know,
it's catastrophic. Um,
I don't know. It's It was a bad look for
Steve Whit.
>> It was a bad look. He was used as a
prop. And And Mike Huckabe looked
ridiculous, too. He looked like Jared
Kushner when Kushner went to Iraq and
was the only person wearing a a
bulletproof vest and it was too small
for him.
Never forget that.
>> Yeah, I know. He reminded me of Dukakus
in the camp in the in the tank.
>> Yeah, in the tank. Um,
notice that nothing came out of this
so-called visit, right? No new
announcement of additional food aid. Uh,
listen, the the the least efficient way
to deliver food to people is to drop it
from planes, right? You drop enough food
for 200 people. Well, there are two
million that are starving,
>> so you're not really helping anybody.
>> Um, but they they came back. They went
back to Jerusalem and nobody said
anything about, you know, opening
opening land bridges or or additional
trucks or nothing.
>> Well, on NPR this um of all places,
there was a really um actually I thought
a very useful report. They interviewed
someone about the food situation in Gaza
who's an expert um at uh I think it was
at Oxfam um and
they said the answer really to like the
high the staggeringly high food prices
in the bazaars is you flood the zone
with food. In other words, it's it's a
supply and demand issue. Um you you just
pour in so much food,
>> more than enough, not minimal, beyond
maximal. Yeah. If you put in so much
food that gazins have to start going on
a diet,
>> yeah,
>> all the prices are going to collapse, no
armed gangs aren't going to be
interested in stealing this food because
it's not going to be valuable anymore.
It's just going to be food. Uh and and
that's the answer here. Um but the
Israelis of course don't want to do
that. Or more accurately, Netanyahu's
right-wing partners in his war cabinet
don't want to do that. I was in uh the
National Whistleblower Day um events day
before yesterday and uh somebody else
mentioned what Dana Alrech is mentioning
right now. American vet and civilian
contractor in Gaza, Anthony Akilar, I
guess is how you say his name, um is
blowing the whistle on what's happening
with with food aid there. um
watch watch that page because uh I think
we're going to get a lot more people
especially Americans
who probably went into this thing being
pro-Israel and anti-Hamas and but still,
you know, wanting to deliver food to
hungry people and they're coming back
like, "Oh my god, it's a genocide. We
have to do something to stop it right
now." And by the way, the Israelis are
stealing the food. Agular. Thank you.
Thank you. That's right.
>> So, I did want to put this up here.
Houdini. Allegedly, there's a square
kilometer full of food and other aid on
the
>> I've heard that.
>> Some of which is probably rotting in the
sun.
>> Yeah.
>> Um but yes, that's because the Israelis
won't let it through. And you know, the
human rights groups that want to
distribute the aid there, like World
Food Kitchen, are not being assured that
they will have more of their workers
killed by the Exactly. Uh thank you,
Spectrum. Thank you very much.
And by the way, um, over on Rumble,
Spectrum is, uh, asking I like I love
this question. Seeing that sanctions
don't work against Russia now, the first
countries that are are discussing
sanctions against Israel, would those
have a better chance of working, yay or
nay?
>> You know what? I think not so much
sanctions
as much as cutting off the billions and
billions of dollars in welfare
>> that we give the the Israelis and and
the uh the weapons.
>> Yeah,
>> they have their own weapons industry.
What do they need our weapons for? But
getting back to the other issue, um I
I briefly worked with an a a woman who
was a dualisraeli British citizen. Um I
didn't like or respect her at all. She
made a comment once during a a coffee
break that her exact words were, "Work
doesn't fit into my lifestyle."
And I was like, "Oh my god, wow." like I
couldn't even Anyway, besides that, um
she told me that she was moving to
Israel. And I said, "Why?
>> You're British. You were born and raised
in the UK."
>> Yeah.
>> And she said, "Because if I move to
Israel, I get a free apartment. I get
free furniture. I get a check every
month to cover my expenses. Food,
transportation, utilities,
everything is free."
>> And they're getting the money from us.
>> They're getting money from us. It's our
taxpayer money.
>> I'm paying $5,100 a month for a
twobedroom.
I I'm, you know, I don't have free
healthcare.
>> That's right.
>> I mean, no, that's absurd. Yeah. No, I
mean,
>> yeah. Outrageous.
>> Yeah. They're a state and like and and
you know, let's let's put them to work
doing something useful, not killing
>> gazins,
>> right? That's right.
>> Oh my god. So insanely nuts. Um, oh,
Michael, Michael Gardner's making a
point here, too. That is important, and
it's exactly right. That's more of an
issue with our military-industrial
complex than anything. It's a win-win
for them and their customers. Israel is
just another customer. Absolutely true.
>> And after 911, I say this all the time,
before 911,
there were more millionaires per capita
in Silicon Valley than anywhere else in
America.
After 911, there were more millionaires
in Washington DC per capita than any
other place in America because that's
where the defense and intelligence
contractors are. And everybody got rich.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, I mean that's that is of
course it's just a business, right? It's
that old war is a racket. Just no
question about it. Um no, I'm glad that
that that that came up. Um, so we're
hearing amid all of this chaos that
Israel clearly not having learned its
lesson yet. Um, got to give them points
for uh, consistency,
>> they're now preparing a new ground
offensive against Gaza. Um, what ground,
John, are they hoping to recapture that
they haven't pre previously recaptured
multiple times? And what are they going
to do with this groundly
leveled everywhere? Yeah, honest to God,
they have flattened all of Gaza. There
is not a single functioning hospital.
Most apartment buildings have been
destroyed. The electrical grid doesn't
work. What was what little grid they
had? There's no clean water. They've
destroyed all of the the bazaars for
people to go buy food. Now, they're just
set up wherever they can set up. There's
nothing left to destroy. So, what they
>> There's something that they did, right?
So, so we you've seen this. Well, okay.
So, we've we've both been to war zones
and usually some buildings are survive
and that's what happened in Gaza from
the aerial. They started with the aerial
bombardment, but a bunch of buildings
survived. Then the IDF came in by ground
and they set up um they they detonated
and blew up using dynamite. They
demolished everything that survived. Uh,
and then they came over and they graded
it with earth movers. Um, and they just
flattening it all out to turn it into a
giant construction site, right?
>> So, is this simply the idea is they're
going to just build on top of it. Why
would they not want to keep any of the
old buildings? I mean, wouldn't it save
money if they're planning to steal the
land, ethnically cleanse it? I'm 100%
convinced that that's been their agenda
all along. Yeah. if that but why not
keep any of the old infrastructure or do
or is this really like also like
psychologically we're going to erase any
trace that these people were ever here
no one's ever going to be able to say
that wall over there was here before
>> that was my family home that's all
that's left yeah no I think that's what
I think that's why they're doing it
they're doing it because you know in the
west we see articles all the time their
memes on Facebook or where have you of
um you know Palestinians standing
outside a house that used to be theirs
and there are these Israeli settlers
from New Jersey that are living in it
now. And I think that they just don't
want that to happen. I think they intend
fully and this is this is you know
ethnic cleansing. It's a genocide to
bulldoze everything so that nothing is
left and build it back from scratch. I
hope I'm wrong. I really do.
>> I don't see how you can be. I mean,
because nothing else makes sense. Yeah.
I mean, they're literally willing to
spend more money
>> to do it this way.
>> A lot more money.
>> I mean, if you think about a city like
Constantinople, which is, you know, is
it like you can see all the layers of of
history there.
>> Oh my god. Yeah.
>> You can still see you can still see the
the walls of the ancient city. You can
still see remnants of the original chain
that the Byzantines ran across the the
Golden Horn to stop ships until they
paid their toll.
>> That's right. Yeah. No, it's so cool.
And they tried to Yeah. Sultan uh Sultan
Attain
so he could get him to conquer in 1453.
So cool. That's at the military museum
>> in Istanbul. Um but anyway, the point is
it's like you can see all those layers
of history in every city that's been
through a war. I mean, even in
Hiroshima, right, there's the there's
some buildings that survive the uh the
the American atomic bomb,
>> but the Israelis really are I mean,
this, by the way, that's genocidal in
character, like erasing all traces that
a culture ever existed there. It's Nazi
style.
The Nazis used to do that in Jewish
neighborhoods where they'd burn
everything down, bulldoze everything, uh
because they didn't want it ever to, you
know, that used to be the Jewish
neighborhood.
>> Yes. Yes. That's right, man. It's
heartbreaking and it just never gets
>> Thank you, Nadia Margaret, for becoming
a monthly supporter for us.
>> Oh, thank you. Much appreciated. She's
number two, assuming she's a she. Um All
right. And if you're not a she, I
apologize. Um, unless you're becoming a
she, in which case I don't apologize. So
complicated. Um, so all right, I guess
we're gonna we're gonna leave Gaza there
or um is there anything else to talk
about there? Are we
>> there? There was a switching to politics
for a minute if I could. I was curious.
I almost called you yesterday
>> because I wanted to get your opinion on
on um
>> Oh, I know.
bird.
>> Kamela Harris is not running for
governor of California.
>> Yeah.
>> Um and and she was just so completely
and utterly insincere in her
explanation. Um she said that um she
just needed some downtime and she needs
to write a book about her experiences.
Of course, she's not writing a book.
They've already hired a ghost writer.
Um, but she she needs to think about
this book and she wants to travel around
the country and meet some of the people
that she did not have a chance to meet
because the campaign was so historically
short. And I thought, "Oh, you are so
full of shit." And I had forgotten how
much I had forgotten how annoying that
nasely nagging voice is. Oh, I never
could. And she sounds Yeah, she she
would sound insincere ordering a beer
and a burger at a restaurant. I mean,
she's Yeah, she's got a very
>> cloying kind of mean, you know, mean. Um
Well, so so okay, we know she's not
running for governor. I knew she wasn't
going to run for governor. I my friends,
you know why? Because being governor is
hard work.
>> It's hard work. And have we learned
nothing from Richard Nixon in 1962?
>> Right. Right. that you you won't have
Kla Harris to kick around anymore. My
mother wore a cloth coat.
>> So, yeah. So, she's not running for
governor. Um, that's not surprising.
Now, everybody's saying, "Well, she'll
run for president again." I don't think
so. I don't think I don't think that's
it at all.
>> If she has a half a brain, she won't run
for president.
>> She won't.
>> She didn't even make it to the Iowa
caucuses the first time.
>> No. No. It would be it would be
catastrophic. Uh she didn't get much
love here from uh and I think even
within the Democratic party, she's just
not I don't even think she could get the
nomination.
>> I don't either. I don't either.
>> There's too many better candidates. Pete
Buddha Judge is the man to beat in 2028.
If you're a Democrat in my opinion, um I
think they're going to they want to
nominate him. He's the DNC pick, I
think.
>> God, I I hope you're wrong, but
>> but I think you're right. And I'll I'll
add too that, you know, she's going to
have Nuome to worry about.
>> Yes.
>> But she's going to have Pritsker to
worry about, too.
>> Yes.
>> And Pritskar is a tough mean guy with an
unlimited supply of money.
>> She will not have Josh Shapiro to worry
about because he zionisted himself out
of the race forever and ever. He'll
never be in national politics. Listen, I
if even if Josh Shapiro and I agreed on
100% of the issues, I would not vote for
him just because he volunteered to serve
in the IDF.
>> Me, too. And then there's um what? Andy
Basher, who you know, if ever there was
a vice presidential candidate, that's
him.
>> He's the guy. He's the perfect one.
>> Yeah, he is.
>> He's he's already like set up a little
exploratory committee. He's already
raising money. He's been to uh New
Hampshire. He went two weeks ago.
>> Yeah,
>> he's a good pick for that. I don't think
she'll run for president because first
of all, she will be smart enough to
listen to all of her advisers who tell
her you can't get the nomination. You'll
humiliate yourself. Yeah, it'll look
really bad. Just just don't. So, I think
she only has two paths.
>> She can uh she can either go to MSNBC,
>> definitely.
>> I think that's too much work. She's not
a hardworking person. So I think she
ends up in a synicure in academia.
University of California trustee.
>> That's what she's doing now.
>> Provost at Pepperdine University.
>> Oh yeah. She's a visiting professor at
Stanford Law School right now.
>> It's the Hillary Clinton. She She's
completely cut and pasted from Hillary
Clinton, right? She's going on a
listening tour. That's what Hillary
Clinton did when she ran for Senate from
New York when everybody hated her and
they were all gonna v vote for the guy
from Long Island instead. Right.
>> Um, whose name escapes me right now. Um,
Rick Lazio.
>> Rick Lazio. Oh my gosh. I haven't heard
that.
>> He was a sacrificial lamb and she almost
and he almost ate the big bad wolf from
>> he almost beat her. That's right.
>> And uh well, you know, he was he's
actually a very likable guy. Uh and um
so I could see why he he kind of did
better than they expected. But yeah,
she's and then of course Hillary was a
professor
>> at at Columbia University School of
International Affairs.
>> That's right. God, I hate to think of
this diplomats of the future being
trained by that harpy.
>> Oh my god.
>> Um, Houdini says she'll she'll be on the
board of some Fortune 500 company. You
bet she will.
>> Maybe. No, it won't be one.
>> It'll be several. Yeah. Yeah, that's
right.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, Michael Gardner says Pritsker is my
governor and I think he'd be a great
candidate.
>> Yeah. A couple of people are are saying
nice things about Pritsker. I like
>> he can donate to himself, too. He's rich
as [__] He
>> He's a billionaire. Yeah, I I like
Pritskar and I like the Pritsker family.
They've they've done a lot of good
stuff.
>> Oh my god, Dana.
>> Maybe she'll end up on the view. Oh,
that's that's good. He wouldn't have to
work except she'd have to be up really
really early in the morning.
>> Hey, getting back to Buddha Judge for a
second. Michelle and I when we had our
show on um on Sputnik, we used to [__]
on Buddha Judge at every opportunity
just because this guy
>> because he's a worm.
>> He was the worst transportation
secretary in American history.
>> Mhm.
>> And he had he had opportunity after
opportunity after opportunity to do
something right. But the the train
derails and spills chemicals in East
Palestine, Ohio. He's on vacation in
Portugal. The the trains go on strike.
He's on vacation in Brazil. Uh what was
it? It was some other strike.
>> Don't forget he took six months off for
paternity leave. Paternity
>> leave in his first year in office. And
like you could say, and it's not like,
you know, they got knocked up
accidentally. It was a surrogate. It was
planned.
>> Exactly. Exactly. Yes. So,
>> so yeah, I I mean this guy I listen he's
he's brilliant. He speaks 55 languages
or whatever. He speaks like eight
languages or whatever.
>> Yeah, he's he was a road scholar. Um
he's a decorated, you know, military
guy. Awesome. Very very smart.
>> Worst in the military, wasn't he
basically a supply clerk? He was like
Radar O'Reilly, wasn't he?
>> Oh, was he?
>> Yeah. I don't think he would. I mean, I
think, you know, he he saw I don't think
he saw many shots fired in anger.
>> Oh my god.
>> You know, but here's the thing. Okay, so
I think people will look back and say
like I did. I always I always made fun
of Mayor Pete because it's like they
made a guy who was the mayor of
Southbend, Indiana. Yeah. The head of
the US Department of Transportation.
Now, here's the funny part. I looked
into this. So, the mayor of Southbend
doesn't control a single piece of mass
transit. As it turns out, Southbend has
a separate transit authority that is not
administered by the mayor. So, he had he
didn't have 0.1% in experience. He had
no experience, right? But, so that said,
um, no one's going to go back and say,
uh, what did you, you know, how come we
don't have highspeed rail, right? I
think they're going to look back at the
train thing maybe and then he'll be
they'll be able to say, you know, this I
was under Biden. Biden didn't let anyone
do anything. He was [__] up and dying.
Then we might say, "Well, what did you
know about Biden?" And he'll say, "Well,
I was the DOT guy. I didn't hang with
him all the time." And that's fairly
credible. So, and we know that he they
hid him.
>> They hid Biden from Buddha Judge and
other members of the cabinet. I mean,
Pete Buddha Judge didn't see Biden for
two years. He lay eyes on him,
>> but that's actually quite common. Do you
remember when Ronald Reagan greeted his
own secretary of housing and urban
development with hello Mr. Mayor and the
guy had been the secretary of of HUD for
eight years?
>> Well, he sat in this in the in the
cabinet meetings with him. You would
think he'd be like who's the guy down at
the end other end of the table past the
defense secretary, right? But yeah, no,
it's Cap Weinberger. Um it it's very
like uh but still I think so here's the
brief for Buddha Judge. I think
handicapping it politically. Uh I think
the brief is he's Obama 2.0.
>> Yeah.
>> So he's professorial, he's calm,
>> very very intelligent.
>> He's intelligent. He doesn't sound
anything like Donald Trump. Every
election is a reaction to the last
president. Um and so and for the so he
gets the nomination I think easily
because the party's obsessed with
identity politics and making history.
Okay, we tried ladies not one but twice,
lost. got to go back to a dude, but we
can't just have a white dude. Oh, but
he's gay. So, we can make that work. And
he's not queeny or flamboyant.
>> No.
>> So, it'll be fine.
>> That's that's that's how he gets the
nomination. That doesn't get him to
1600,
>> but it gets him the nomination.
>> That's my take.
>> First of all, thank you, Firmware Chip
from Wake Forest. Thank you for that
generosity. Um, and and there are a lot
of really good comments here about, you
know, he he is a vet who's not draped in
the flag, which is refreshing. He's very
intelligent.
He's the anti-Trump in like practically
every way.
>> True.
>> Um, he's a great speaker. Um, he would
be able to go toe-to-toe in a debate
with with Vance.
>> True.
>> Jay Vance is a good debater.
>> True. Oh. Oh, yeah. He he just he ate
Kla Harris,
>> but being gay. I mean
>> I mean you know
>> what what about like the the Bernie
Trump
>> sorry Tim Walls. He ate Tim Walls.
That's who it was.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Um what about the Bernie
Trump voters? People who voted for
Bernie and then voted for Trump. They're
not going to they're not going to vote
for a gay man. I I don't think
>> I don't think Well, I don't think Buddha
Judge isn't going to get the progressive
left of the Democratic party. And that's
why I wouldn't
>> unless he needs but he he can still but
he won't he's he's a DNC pick so they
won't let him come out against Israel
and they won't let him come out in favor
of like uh you know Medicare for all the
Bernie stuff. If he can grab the the
progressive stuff
>> he's in in like Flynn.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I don't know.
>> We need we need somebody who's a who's a
bonafide progressive.
>> Yeah. Who's the highest ranked? I'm
trying to think who's the highest ranked
um openly gay American politician. Um
we've had a bunch of congressmen. Um we
had we had a closeted senator from
Idaho.
>> Well, we've got
>> same thing.
>> We've got
>> the senator from Wisconsin. I forget her
name.
>> Oh, right. Um Tammy Baldwin or whatever.
>> Tammy B. Is it Tammy Baldwin who's gay?
>> No. Is it the other one? I think
>> Yeah, I think it's the other one.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh you know what? I don't know. To
answer your question, do we have any gay
governors?
>> That's a good question.
No one's I've always I've always thought
uh I've always thought that uh Ronda
Santis was closeted, but that might just
be his voice. I don't know. People
thought that I was gay, too. It's like,
you know, when I used to have open mic
Friday, open mic day on my old radio
show in LA, the one open mic question
was always, "Ted, are you gay?" Always.
And I didn't want to deny it because I
thought that would be like homophobic
like you know.
>> Sure.
>> Sort of like nah. So I just be like I
don't want to talk about it. I'm not
gonna say yay. I'm not gonna say nay.
Yeah. Tammy Duckworth. I don't know if
that's her.
>> Is it Tammy Duckworth?
>> I don't know.
>> No. Tammy Duckworth is the war hero,
isn't she?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, you can be you can be
gay and be a war hero.
>> No, but I mean but she lost her legs and
she's from Isn't she from Illinois?
>> God. Um I'm gonna have to I'm gonna I'm
gonna look this up like
Okay. The lesbian senator is Tammy
Baldwin.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Tammy Baldwin from Wisconsin.
>> Too many Tammies.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Lots of Tamies. And And the
new senator from uh or the new What is
she? The governor of
>> Good point.
>> Arizona. She's by
>> America. Peter Teal is gay and more
powerful than any politician. No doubt.
>> Yeah. I don't know. I I I don't really
focus. You know, I said to my I said to
my daughter not too long ago, one of the
things that I admire about this
generation is that is that they don't
stovepipe themselves into these
these, you know, gay, straight, by this,
that u I I I I'm from the stovepipe
generation.
I can't I can't relate to the whole like
>> it's hard. I don't know. I don't fully
understand it.
>> Like I I I have to admit I don't believe
in people are gender fluid. I mean, I
know it's true. I know people who know
people who swear that it's true, but I
can't believe it. It's like, okay, so if
it's 10 o'clock in the morning, um
feeling like uh I'm gay, and if it's
like 10:45, I'm straight and maybe I
don't want sex at all by, you know, by
noon. I don't know. I just don't get it.
>> There's
>> I don't care, but it's just weird.
There's a guy that that we worked with,
Ted. I I'm not going to out him, of
course, but um over dinner, he just
casually said that he was pansexual.
>> Oh, right.
>> I said, you know, I've I've heard the
term. I I'm not sure I fully understand
it. And he said, um he said, I'll I'll
have sex with anybody that seems
attractive to me. Men, women, women
dressed as men, men dressed as women.
He said, it makes no difference to me.
Uh I I knew a Russian guy who did not
work with us who used he I remember
hearing him talk to someone like that
and he says, "You are not you are
omnivorous. You are greedy.
>> All right. I mean, you know, as long as
long as they're over 18. You guys do
you. I don't care.
>> I I have a very short story I have to
tell. So there was um there was an
editor that we used to work with at
Sputnik years ago who I liked very much
and who I sat next to um them. Okay. So
um
one day
when he was a he came into work with
just a little bit of blue eyeshadow and
I thought, "Huh, that's kind of
different." All right. Well, none of my
business. And then after a couple of
weeks of that, um, came in with a blouse
and blue jeans and I thought, "Oh, okay.
They're transitioning. Okay." And then
after a while, it was very stylish
dresses and, you know, woman. And then
he changed his Twitter bio to she, her,
and then later to she, they. Okay. So,
I was asked to give a speech at the
Venezuelan embassy the night that we
broke off diplomatic relations with the
Venezuelans. So, I I was there with a
bunch of people. There was like a riot
outside and this young woman came up to
me and she said, "Hi, John. We haven't
met, but my name is, you know, Mary. I'm
so husband. I'm sorry. I'm so and so's
wife. And I said, "Oh, I'm sorry. I
didn't even know they were married."
So, we had a nice little chat. I go to
the office the next day and um
and our colleague comes in and says,
"Hey, I heard you had a chance to meet
Mary last night." And I said, "Oh, yeah.
We had a lovely conversation." I said,
"I apologize. I didn't know you were
gay."
and they say, "I'm not gay."
And I said, "Oh, I'm sorry, but your
your Twitter bio says that you're a
woman and you're married to a woman."
>> So,
I said, "Well, I thought that meant
>> by definition,
>> yeah, that if you're a woman and you're
married to another woman that that
you're gay." And
he says, you know, it's your generation
that wants to put labels on everybody.
>> I was like, okay,
>> okay. Well, there's just there they are
words. I mean, it does not matter.
>> Yeah, that's pretty funny. Um,
>> all right. So, we've got a little
another ad and I think and there's one
last story that uh I want to talk to you
here. I'm going to read this. I'll do
you want to do the ad or I can read the
ad.
>> Oh, go right ahead. I don't have it.
>> Okay. When Rumble first started in 2013,
they built the platform for the small
creator. They didn't censor or have
biases. They were fair and treated all
creators equally. No one thought
platforms would censor political
conversation or censor opinions on
COVID, but they did. Facebook admitted
they fell to pressure from the Biden
Harris administration. Rumble did not.
They held the line. They attacked daily
for giving us a voice to talk to you.
They're attacked in corporate media.
They're attract They're attacked by
governments like France. They're
attacked from brand advertisers who
refuse to work with them. Corporate
America is fighting to remove speech.
Rumble is fighting to keep it. Rumble
won't survive with band with brand
advertisers. They don't get much of it.
It's watching the show on Rumble is the
most they can ask from you. But if you
really believe in this fight and you
have the means, one major way you can
help Rumble survive is by joining Rumble
Premium. Join the community that
believes in the First Amendment and
believes in our human right to free
speech, Rumble's offering 10 bucks off
with the promo code studio. When you
purchase an annual subscription, go to
rumble.com/premium and use pro promo
code studio. Like I said, if you have
the means and believe in the cause, now
is the time to join Rumble. Um, and I
think that's okay. I guess that's it for
that ad. All right. So, uh, John, I
wanted to talk to you about
microlastics. Uh, I know it's not really
our wheelhouse, but why not?
Everything's our wheelhouse. So, a new
study came out that found that if you
just sit at home,
your body absorbs an average of 68,000
discrete microlastical
plastic particles every single day.
>> How crazy is that?
>> It's crazy.
>> But it's happening.
>> Look, I'm drinking out of a plastic
bottle right now.
>> Right.
>> Yeah. So we should I mean it's like so
many things that are going on in our
society and the political class doesn't
seem to even address it. I mean you
don't even hear Bernie Sanders talk
about this, right? I mean we need we
need political figures like you know I
loved how I had many problems with him
but I loved how Al Gore was obsessed
with climate change and took it upon
himself to educate the public. Um and it
didn't unfortunately do much but he
tried. Yeah. Um, you know, I I would
love to see whether it's Pete Buddha
Judge or some other candidate, hell,
Donald Trump, any anybody,
>> JD Vance take up this cause, you know.
>> Yeah. And nobody is. And it's funny, the
experts are shouting it from the
rooftops. You're right. The politicians
aren't responding or reacting in any
way. And usually when there's this
consensus in in a community,
some politician is going to pick it up
as an issue and nobody seems to care.
They just accept it like, "Oh, well, you
know, I was talking to a to a funeral
director the other day. That was my
phone, by the way, on the and now I
can't duplicate the sound." Anyway, um I
was talking to a funeral director who I
know and he told me that we eat so many
ultrarocessed foods over the course of a
lifetime that even some people who don't
get inbalmed
stay intact for years.
>> Oh my god.
>> Yeah. Because of all the preservatives.
>> That's disgusting.
>> It's disgusting.
I mean, this is where Well, I guess
look, honestly, part many uh
progressives voted for Trump because of
RFK Jr.
>> and and Maha. He's been really quiet. Is
this one of those things where there's,
you know, several possibilities? The two
big ones, I think, are either
>> Donald Trump just hogs the limelight and
doesn't let anyone else talk and or um
RFK Jr. is in the trenches rolling up
his sleeves and working on something big
and it's just not ready to be announced
yet.
>> Yeah, that may that may very well be it.
Yeah. And you know, I think that he's
still facing such push back from
Democrats.
Oh, you know what?
Somebody just wrote,
um, I bet John knows where to bury the
bodies. And I responded
>> and it rejected my response.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. It says, "This comment will not be
posted to deprogram show."
>> That's awesome.
>> I said, "The mob taught me that you bury
them under somebody else's casket."
>> Oh, this is funny. We were talking about
Ed. Poor Edia mean he he wouldn't be
able to eat now.
>> No.
>> No. Oh my god.
>> Eat McDonald's and you'll be buried like
a pharaoh.
>> Seriously. so much for our McDonald's uh
ads that we were hoping to get. Um yeah,
by the way, this is tr totally true.
Being a dive instructor, I see the
impact plastic has on our environment a
lot. It's bad. Like really bad. Pulled
out plastic straps from a turtle's
mouth.
>> I'm a diver. Um, John, and I I got to
tell you, um, even in just the 25 years
or so that I've been diving, um, it's
the reefs have gone from basically dying
to dead all over. It's really hard to
find a reef where there's any fish or
anything going on. Um it's uh you know
and and it's true like you can go to a
remote island uh where there's a
population of like a hundred in the
Caribbean and like the the side where
the current hits will be completely
filled with trash that uh and plastic
bottles that have washed in across the
Atlantic Ocean. Um it's you know it's
it's really really
>> Yeah, we have that plastic island in the
Pacific that Dana is referring to. It's
the size of Texas. There's one in the
Atlantic, too, now.
>> Oh, I didn't know that.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my god.
Terrible. Well,
>> well,
>> yeah. No, it's uh it's it's pretty
grad
I'm not I can't even like comment on
that one. Um All right. I'm trying to
think. Is there anything else that we
need to talk about here? Oh, I guess
we'd be remiss if we didn't talk about
uh Trump repositioning those two nuclear
submarines. So we could leave that lead
out bring it out with that one. Um, do
we care about that? I mean, or is that
just I mean, how important is that,
John? I
>> I don't think it is important. It's It's
meant to intimidate. Um, but like I've
said in the past, if if we're serious
about about a fight, we reposition
entire carrier battle groups. A couple
of subs are just meant to sort of piss
them off. Maybe scare them a little bit
that they're not going to be scared. But
it it was just what what a president who
is kind of impotent in this in this
situation might do.
>> It it just seemed completely symbolic. I
mean, I was also like I mean, do you
think Vladimir Putin woke up one morning
and like Joe Biden forgot about our
ICBM's arsenal?
>> I mean, if we want to nuke them, we
can't.
>> Seriously. Right. Seriously.
>> Oh. Oh, not the submarines.
>> Yeah. I'm scared now.
>> Now, now they're angry.
>> All right, John. Um, I think we're gonna
leave that there. Yeah.
>> Well, I want to say thanks again to
everybody. Thank you for your
generosity, for spending this hour with
us every uh every other day, soon to be
every day. We literally can't do this
without you. So, thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Seriously, thank you. Um and so again,
Monday, Wednesday, Friday, 5:00 pm
Eastern time. I'm Ted R. John Kuryaku
drogram. We'll be back Monday at 5:00
p.m. and uh we'll deprogram you from uh
all the news and the spin and [__]
about the news that breaks over the
weekend. Thanks again and take care.